Amadeus Folego Curriculum vitae

## AMADEUS FOLEGO DA SILVA

Born in Mauá, SP, 23/12/1988 - Single Aurora St. 787, ap. 52, São Paulo - SP, 01209-001

CONTACT INFO Email: amadeusfolego@gmail.com Phone: 55 11 94807-0450

Github: @badosu

PROFILE Versatile professional, with experience developing for the web using many technologies.

Interested in Math, Computer Science, Audio Processing and *Hacking* in general. Has familiarity, and good learning skills, for concepts and technologies which are

relevant for the web.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

10/2014 Presumé http://presume.com.br

Technical partner at Presumé: a platform for pre-interviewing candidates.

08/2015 - 03/2016 Pegcar http://pegcar.com

Peer-to-peer car sharing service. Co-founded and created the website that is

still running today.

12/2013 - 10/2014 Stackbuilders http://stackbuilders.com

Web development consultancy company based on NY. Many different projects.

05/2013 - 10/2013 Palpiteros http://palpiteros.com

A football social platform, built with Backbone, RoR and some other tools.

11/2012 - 04/2013 ClickARQ http://clickarq.com.br

Architecture crowdsourcing startup, where I worked as CTO and the only developer.

**06/2012 - 12/2012 Codeminer42** http://codeminer42.com

Worked in several startup projects, with Ruby, Java and Python.

06/2010 - 05/2012 Boo-box, Betboo

Previous workplaces, started doing web-development with .Net and Ruby.

## **PROJECTS**

- Statesman Sequel https://github.com/badosu/statesman-sequel Statesman adapter for Sequel
- **Binding of caller** http://rubydoc.info/gems/binding\_of\_caller/ Helped implement the JRuby and Rubinius versions.
- Sine Synth https://github.com/badosu/sine\_synth.lv2
  A sine waveform synthesizer

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

01/2010 (unfinished) B.Sc. Mathematics Universidade Federal do ABC

2006 B.Sc. Science and Technology Universidade Federal do ABC

Dynamic modelling of the Magnetic Hysteresis phenomenon
 Available at (pt-br): http://www.scribd.com/doc/21709933